[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is the reason why vegetarian diet is good for humans.", "correct_answer": "Anatomically, humans resemble herbivores", "incorrect_answers": ["Meat is slightly toxic", "Humans were herbivores at the beginning of their existence", "Fruits and vegetables remain in the intestines longer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At the end of his historic performance at the Monterey Pop Festival in 1967, this musician set his guitar Fender Stratocaster on fire.", "correct_answer": "Jimi Hendrix", "incorrect_answers": ["Little Richard", "Janis Joplin", "Peter Townsend"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What movie is this quote from: \u201cCalm down everybody. Were just here to negotiate General Sarris surrender.?", "correct_answer": "Galaxy Quest", "incorrect_answers": ["Mad Labs", "Alcatraz Escape", "Star Wars"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these terms is used to describe one of the scenarios concerning the end of the world?", "correct_answer": "Grey goo", "incorrect_answers": ["Red goo", "Brown goo", "Yellow goo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Containers used for disposing of needles and other sharp objects must be all of the following except which one?", "correct_answer": "Recyclable", "incorrect_answers": ["Disposable", "Clearly Marked bio-hazard", "Puncture resistant"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This Australian monotreme lays eggs and has a remarkable sense of electroception.", "correct_answer": "Platypus", "incorrect_answers": ["Red kangaroo", "Dingo", "Emu"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Complete this quote: Apres moi , le ......", "correct_answer": "Deluge", "incorrect_answers": ["Direz", "Denouement", "Dirge"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Barbers traditionally have red and white poles in front of their stores because in the Middle Ages they did the blood letting.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which famous writer introduced the term moron into everyday vocabulary?", "correct_answer": "Moliere", "incorrect_answers": ["Voltaire", "Shakespeare", "Dickens"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is not a nickname for a polar bear?", "correct_answer": "Great bear", "incorrect_answers": ["White bear", "Northern bear", "Sea bear"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What happens to Tom Cruises character in the 2006 movie Mission: Impossible III?", "correct_answer": "He becomes a father.", "incorrect_answers": ["He accidentally kills his cat.", "All of these", "He gets married."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the literal meaning of the word raccoon, which originates from the Algonquin word ahrah-koon-em and denotes a scavenging mammal?", "correct_answer": "One who rubs, scrubs and scratches with its hands", "incorrect_answers": ["One who grasps with their hand just like a human", "One who eats whatever is in front of them", "One who washes their hands and their food before eating"]}]